ELIZABETH WELCH

OBJECTIVE

A background in graphic design with a focus on web design, coupled with training in web development and computer programming makes me a great asset to any team requiring a programmer with an eye for user experience. My work would idealy allow me to use my education to its fullest, though a focus on programming is preferred.

SKILLS

Programming:

- Languages: HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, C++, C#, VB.NET
- Microsoft SQL Server Management Studio
- Bootstrap
- ASP.NET MVC

Design:

- Web Design
- Adobe Creative Suite
 - Illustrator
 - Photoshop
 - InDesign

Other:

- Capable of organizing groups of people by assigning tasks that focus on strengths while minimizing weaknesses
- Organize and self-motivated worker

EDUCATION

Computer Programmer

Durham College, April 2018 Two Year Diploma, Dean's List

B.A., Graphic Design

Portland State University, December 2013 Earned with a focus on Web Design

WORK EXPERIENCE

Database Development Research Assistant

Durham College ORSIE January 2018-Present

Created new database architecture from scratch to serve as the new home of a company's existing 20+ year old system using Microsoft SQL Server Management Studio, to improve report speeds and allow for future database growth.

Web Development and UX Research Assistant

Durham College ORSIE January 2018-April 2018

Worked alongside one other student to create a MVC based product website. Focus was mostly on front-end coding and user experience.

Web Development and UX Research Assistant

Durham College ORSIE

February 2017-July 2017

Worked with multiple teams of student workers to develop systems to client specifications.

One project was front and back-end programming for a company's landing page, the other was focused on Android application development and user experience.

Freelance Illustration

Freelance/Self-employed
February 2015-July 2016
Created illustrations and designs for clients.

Food Service Supervisor

Cascadia Market at Oregon State University

April-June, 2014 & September, 2014-January, 2015

Kept sales floor organized, created sales displays, directed & kept workers on task, assisted customers.

VOLUNTEER/OTHER EXPERIENCE

Friendtorship

October 2013-December 2013

Portland State University

Worked with high schoolers from Centennial Park School to make art and help nurture creativity.

Organized and ran workshops with the students.